mooji.tv 2019-05-05

# Privacy Policy - Mooji TV

  1. **Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to us. This policy explains what types of personal information will be gathered when you visit the www.mooji.tv website (the “Website”), including when you register online, when you contact us or when you provide to us any piece of personal data, directly or inside an electronic form. Personal data means information or pieces of information that could allow us to identify you. 

  1. **Information Collected**

We may collect the following personal data: your name, email address, preferences and feedback, your IP address or information about your use of our Website, but also any other information you provide voluntarily to us.  
We collect personal data in order to provide you with certain services related to:

• opening an account, processing your application, processing an order, sending you an invoice for our service,

• your access to Sahaja Express or any other Website service,

• your request for Satsang Support,

• for survey purposes (in order to adjust and develop our activity),

• the sharing/transferring (for example by means of an assignment/merger) services within the Sangha entities and/or for integrating and reorganising them into new or existing entities, and

• the prevention of potential threats to our service.

We may store this information manually or electronically.

We do not store any credit card details. However, our third party partners through which we process all your payments (if the case) may store such card details. For more information, please carefully read their Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy.

  1. **How the information collected is used**

The personal information you provide to us will only be used for the purposes stated above. Personal information will not be sold to third parties, or provided to direct marketing companies or other such organisations. Personal information collected and/or processed by us is held in accordance with the provisions of the Data Protection Act 1998 of United Kingdom and of Law no.67/1998 of Portugal and of EU General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679.

  1. **How we store information collected and for how long**

Information which you provide to us will ordinarily be stored on our secure servers. However, we do work with third party contractors, some of whom host and operate certain features of the Website. Accordingly, your personal data may be collected in or transferred to a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). That information may be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our contractors.

By using the Website, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing. We will take all steps reasonably possible to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

For specific services, such as Sahaja Express, in order to provide you with a secure, efficient and reliable service, the registration process and the payment of your subscription is done through our approved third party vendor, Cleeng. You can view their Privacy policy here: <https://cleeng.com/us/privacy>.

The personal data you disclose through any and all means to us except that data which is included in photography or in any audio/video/audio-video recordings, shall be processed, shared and stored for a period of 5(five) years for the above mentioned purposes. Personal data you submit for Satsang Support (including video and/or audio recordings) shall be kept for a maximum period of 2 years. The personal data disclosed that is included in photography or in any audio/video/audio-video recordings shall be processed, stored or shared for an unlimited period of time and only for educational, informative or promotional purposes of sharing Sri Mooji’s teaching and pointings with the public with the utmost respect and sensitivity.

  1. **Confidentiality Notice**

All personal data disclosed to us shall be treated as confidential by all Sangha entities’ employees, volunteers, assistants and helpers. We have implemented procedures and workflows so that we ensure that your personal data (including possible correspondence with us, Skype calls, recordings of any kind, audio, video, photography, etc) will be treated with utmost respect, taking into account the principle of using your personal data lawfully, fairly and ethically only by specific people for specific purposes where is relevant for their workflow, keeping it secure and at your disposal by request.

  1. **Access to Information**

The law gives you the right to access information held about you. It also gives you the right to object to processing of the data relating to you. You may also request rectification or erasure of your personal data and withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data for one or more purposes. However, in case you decide to withdraw your consent for one or more purposes herein listed, withdrawal which we’ll make us unable to provide you with the service required and/or with any ongoing contractual and/or legal obligations that we may have towards you and/or towards others, we reserve our right to refuse such withdrawal. For further information about such rights and how to exercise them, please write an email to [dataprotection@mooji.org](mailto:dataprotection@mooji.org), providing your full legal name, the information you are requesting access to, the rights you would like to invoke and the reasons for your request. 

  1. **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Any changes we may make to the Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page.

  1. **Cookies policy**

A cookie is a piece of information in the form of a very small text file that is placed on an internet user’s computing device, in order to make the user’s interaction with the website easier, faster and more convenient. We use cookies so that you remain logged in whilst you browse and there are cookies associated with the video and audio files that you access. We may also use other cookies solely for the purpose of enabling you access, use and to personalise the website for you. We do use Google Analytics.

  1. **Contact concerning our Terms and Condition & Privacy Policy**

Any queries or concerns about this Privacy Policy can be sent to [dataprotection@mooji.org](mailto:dataprotection@mooji.org). This Privacy Policy applies equally for the personal data collected by any and all of the following organisations (herein collectively referred to as “Sangha entities”): Mooji Foundation Ltd., Mooji Media Ltd., Associação Mooji Sangha and Jai Sahaja – Alojamento e Comercio de Productos Basicos, LDA.
